Dammit! He isn't holding back! We gotta get outta here!
Kahretsin! Hiç acıması yok! Buradan tüyelim!
This place is done for!
Buranın işi bitti!
So that's where the village of those vile Shandian warriors was hiding?
Demek o aşağılık Shandialı savaşçıların köyü orada saklanıyormuş?
They're originally from the Blue Sea. Surely they'd enjoy going home!
Esasında Mavi Deniz'den gelmeler. Bunu kesinlikle hoş karşılayacaklar.
Now, fall to the world below!
Şimdi, Mavi Deniz'e düşün!
Our village!
Köyümüz!
That was close!
Ucuz atlattık!
We'd have been burnt to a crisp if we had left any later!
Biraz daha bekleseydik, hepimiz ölmüştük.
In the name of Great Warrior Kalgara...
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara adına yemin edin!
shine the Light of Shandora!
Shandora'nın Işığını yakın!
Wyper...
Wyper...
You see, your distant ancestor, Great Warrior Kalgara,
Atan Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara'nın...
had another reason for wanting to take back our homeland.
yurdunu geri almak istemesinin bir sebebi daha vardı.
Another reason?
Bir sebep daha mı?
Indeed.
Evet.
It is Kalgara's single biggest regret.
Kalgara için bu onun en büyük pişmanlığı oldu.
Listen.
Şimdi dinle.
Great Warrior Kalgara had a very close friend...
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara'nın bir can dostu varmış...
A close friend?
Can dostu mu?
Yes. He met Kalgara 400 years ago. His name was...
Evet. 400 yıl önce buraya gelmiş. Adı...
Mont Blanc Noland!
Mont Blanc Noland!
Our tale begins a long, long time ago...
Uzun, uzun zaman evvel...
400 years before the present day...
belki de 400 yıl önce.
and though no written record exists...
Asla yazıya dökülmemiş ama...
the legend lives on from one generation to the next.
duyanların kalplerine kazınmaya devam etmiş bir hikaye...
Get on board, quickly!
Gemiye binin, çabuk!
The Demon of Shandora is coming!
Shandora İblisi ensemizde!
Hurry! Cast off! Cast off!
Çabuk! Yelken açın! Hemen!
But there are still crewmen–
Tayfa henüz gemiye–
Just get us out to sea already!
Hemen denize açılın!
He's here!
Geldi!
You must be eliminated!
Yok edileceksiniz!
Leave all your belongings and go!
Her şeyi bırakıp gidin.
R-Reporting, Commodore!
Komodor, işte raporum!
Our provisions have finally been exhausted,
Erzağımız bitti.
meaning we're now... lost... at sea...
Şu an resmen çok zor... durumdayız...
The cook fainted!
Aşçı bayıldı.
Dammit! There's no food left!
Lanet olsun! Hiç yemek kalmadı!
The commodore dove overboard!
Komodor, denize düştü.
This is the Grand Line!
Burası Grand Line!
Is he gonna drown himself and abandon us?!
Niyeti boğulup bizi terk etmek mi?!
Maybe he was so hungry he chose death instead?
Belki de açlığa dayanamayıp ölmek istedi?
Of course not!
Saçmalık!
He's made it back from the Grand Line twice! He's a legend!
Grand Line'dan iki kez geri dönmeyi başaran bir efsane o!
Then how do you explain these neatly arranged clothes and shoes?!
Peki ya bu özenle bırakılmış kıyafetler ve ayakkabılar?
H-Hey! Someone go check...
H-Hey! Biri gidip baksın...
Screw that!
Olmaz!
This sea is full of monsters!
Bu sular canavarlarla dolu!
He's not coming back up!
Geri dönmeyecek!
– C-Commodore!
– K-Komodor!
He was a pretty nimble guy. Here.
Epey çevikti! Al.
Huh? A rope?
Eh... ip mi?
Reel it in.
Yukarı çekin.
What is this, Commodore?!
Bu nedir, Komodor?!
You killed this thing underwater?!
Yoksa bu şeyi su altında mı öldürdünüz?!
Cook it up for us.
Pişirin.
Slacking off really does dull the senses.
Tembellik gerçekten hisleri köreltiyor.
It's a huge storm, Commodore!
Bu büyük bir fırtına, Komodor!
Sure seems like it with all the swaying.
Bu sallanmayla kesinlikle öyle görünüyor.
"Sure seems like it"? Seriously?!
Öyle mi görünüyor? Cidden mi?!
The yardarm's busted!
Serenimiz* gitti!
Where?!
Nereye?!
The main mast!
Ana direk!
We set out on this voyage a little over two years ago.
Bu üçüncü yolculuğum. İki yıldan fazladır sürüyor.
It's a miracle that we've lasted this long.
Bu kadar uzun süre devam etmiş olmamız bir mucize.
Hey, did you hear that just now?
Hey, şunu duydun mu?
Huh? Do you mean the thunder?
Ha? Yıldırımı mı kastediyorsunuz?
No, it was something beautiful...
Hayır, güzel bir çan sesi...
like a bell...
gibi...
Priest! Stay with us!
Başkeşiş, bizimle kal!
This land is cursed! At this rate, the Shandians will be completely eradicated!
Bu topraklar lanetli! Bu gidişle Shandiyalılar tamamen yok olacak!
H-How can we save the village, Priest?!
K-Köyü nasıl kurtarabiliriz, başkeşiş?!
O-Offer... the girl!
B-Bir kız... sunmalıyız!
At the sacrificial altar!
Adak sunağında!
How many dead does that make?
Ölü sayısı kaç?
Over a hundred...
Yüzden fazla...
What's going on?!
Bu nasıl olabilir?
This has never happened to us before!
Daha önce hiç böyle bir şey olmamıştı!
If I can be of use, I will gladly give my life.
Köyü kurtaracaksa memnuniyetle hayatımı vereceğim.
Why do you cry, Mama?
Niye ağlıyorsun, anne?
I'm about to be welcomed into the Sun God's embrace!
Güneş Tanrısı'yla tanışacağım.
You know being chosen as a sacrifice is a wonderful thing!
Adak olarak seçilmek bir onurdur.
Thank you for raising me, Mama.
Beni bu yaşıma kadar büyüttüğün için teşekkür ederim, anne.
Mousse!
Mousse!
If this is a nightmare, please let me wake up!
Bu kötü bir rüyaysa uyandırın beni!
Dammit!
Lanet olsun!
Go away!
Defol!
Disappear!
Çekil üzerimden!
Great Warrior Kalgara...
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara...
Seto...
Seto...
I wanted to be like you someday...
Bir gün senin gibi olmak istiyordum,
I wanted to fight to protect this land as a brave warrior!
yurdumuzu korumak için dövüşen cesur bir savaşçı!
I don't wanna die because of something like this!
Bu şekilde ölmek istemiyorum!
You're amazing, Commodore!
Harikasınız, Komodor!
There really was an island in these waters!
Bu sularda hakikaten de bir ada varmış!
Yes, what a relief. We can ride out the storm here.
Evet, tam zamanında. Fırtınayı burada atlatabiliriz.
So you guys really didn't hear anything?
Ama gerçekten hiçbiriniz duymadınız mı?
Nope. None of us heard any bells. Right?
Hayır, kimse çan sesi duymadı. Değil mi?
Yeah! You must've been hearing things, Commodore!
Evet! Gaipten sesler duyuyor olmalısınız, Komodor!
What a magnificent forest!
Ne muhteşem bir orman!
I hope we find some good research materials!
Umarım araştırabileceğimiz iyi türler buluruz.
Commodore! Was that the sound you heard?!
Komodor! Duyduğunuz ses bu muydu?!
Hey, now! Don't tease me!
Hey, kesin şunu.
I'd never mistake what I heard earlier for these weird birdcalls!
Az önce duyduğum şeyi asla bu garip kuş sesleriyle karıştırmam!
C-Commodore! Was that...?
K-Komodor! Bu...?
Wow... What a beautiful tone...
Vay be... Ne güzel bir ses...
I knew it! There are people here!
Demek bu adada yerleşim var.
H-Hold on, Commodore! Wait!
Durun, Komodor! Bekleyin biraz!
Someone's on the ground!
Yerde biri var!
Damn it... Intruders!
Olamaz! Davetsiz misafirler...
Hey, kid!
Hey, çocuk...
Commodore! He doesn't look right!
Komodor, bu çocukta bir tuhaflık var!
Hold it, kid!
Dur, hey!
Let go!
Bırakın beni!
It's tree fever.
Ağaç ateşi.
He hasn't been treated at all.
Tedavi edilmemiş.
Th-This island is bad news!
Bu ada sıkıntı!
Doctor! Do we have any conine left?!
Doktor, hiç koniin* kaldı mı?
Inject this boy and the rest of us immediately!
Bu çocuğa ve geri kalanımıza hemen aşı yap!
This is bad.
Bu korkunç.
It's even eating away at the crops...
Ekinler bile etkilenmiş.
Commodore! Everyone inside is sick!
Komodor, bütün köy hasta!
Bring the girl to the altar!
Kızı sunağa getirin!
God of the Sun...
Güneş Tanrısı...
God of the Rain...
Yağmur Tanrısı...
God of the Forest...
Orman Tanrısı...
God of the Earth...
Toprak Tanrısı...
In exchange for this girl's life, please save our village!
Bu kızın hayatına karşılık lütfen köyümüzü kurtar!
It's God Kashi!
Tanrı Kashi!
Mousse!
Mousse!
Let her go! It's for the village!
Yapmamalısın! Köyü kurtarabilir!
God Kashi has such a divine form!
Tanrı Kashi, ne büyüleyici bir şekil.
Please save my mother!
Lütfen annemi kurtar!
Please save my son and father!
Lütfen oğlumu ve babamı kurtar!
What the...?! Something fell!
Ne...?! Bir şey düştü!
What's that?!
O da neydi?
What in the world?! Who is that?!
Ne oldu öyle?! O da kim?!
God Kashi!
Tanrı Kashi!
Godkiller!
Tanrı Katili!
This ceremony is over.
Bu ayin sona ermiştir.
You must've been terrified.
Korkmuş olmalısın.
You're safe now.
Artık güvendesin.
There's no need for you to die.
Ölmen gerekmiyor.
God Kashi! Please forgive us!
Tanrı Kashi! Lütfen bizi bağışla!
We're all going to be cursed!
Hepimiz lanetleneceğiz!
Kill her!
Öldürün onu!
Offer more sacrifices to the gods before we incur their wrath!
Tanrının öfkesine maruz kalmadan önce ona daha fazla can sunun!
Kalgara!
Kalgara!
Kill him!
Öldür onu!
Sounds like he did something bad...
Sanırım kötü bir şey yaptı...
They're really freaking out!
Epey kızmış gibiler!
Commodore... what did you get yourself into now?!
Komodor... şimdi neye bulaştınız?!
He killed a god?
Bir tanrı mı öldürdü?!
What does that mean?!
Bu da ne demek?!
He shouldn't be messing around with tribal rituals!
Kabile ayinine karışmamalıydı!
Quell the wrath of the gods, Great Warrior Kalgara!
Lütfen tanrının öfkesini yatıştır, Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara!
I am an explorer from the North Blue, Mont Blanc No–
Ben Kuzey Mavi'den kaşif, Mont Blanc No–
It doesn't matter who you are!
Kim olduğun umurumda değil!
You must be eliminated!
Yok edileceksin!
Eliminated? Like every crucial ember of progress you've snuffed out?
Sorunlarınızı ucunda gelişim olsa bile böyle mi çözüyorsunuz?
You have no right to preach to us! Atone to the gods where you stand!
Bize vaaz vermeye hakkın yok! Durduğun yerde tanrılara kefaretini öde.
Who is that man?!
Kim bu adam?
He's holding his own against Kalgara!
Kalgara'yla eşit dövüşüyor!
There! Use that knife to take your life!
Al! Bıçağı kullan ve canını feda et!
What?!
Ne?!
You're a sacrifice meant to save our village, yet now you're crying because you want to live.
Köyümüzü kurtaracak olan kurban, kendi hayatı için yalvarıp sızlıyor.
Have you no shame?!
Utanman yok mu?!
Don't be a fool!
Aptal olma!
Stop!
Dur!
C-Commodore!
K-Komodor!
For centuries, the people of this island have upheld the commandment
Bu adanın halkı, yüzyıllar boyunca izinsiz girenlerin...
that all intruders must be punished!
cezalandırılması kuralını sürdürmüştür!
What's more, you are a godkiller!
Üstelik sen bir Tanrı Katili'sin!
Your death alone won't be enough!
Sadece senin ölmen yetmez!
You and all your men will pay with your lives!
Bu iğrençliğin kefaretini ödemek için hepinizin canını alacağız!
"Lives" this, "sacrifices" that!
Tüm mesele hayat ve kurban mı?
Do you think those make your gods happy?!
Tanrılarınızın istediği bu mu?
This ceremony is an affront to humanity's progress!
Bu ayin, insanlığın gelişimine bir hakarettir.
I won't stand for it any longer!
Buna daha fazla katlanmayacağım!
This is an insult to all the adventurers and researchers
Yağtığınız şey, insanlara mutluluk getirme umuduyla denize açılan...
who have set out to sea in the hopes of bringing people happiness!
tüm kaşifler ve araştırmacılar için bir utanç kaynağıdır!
If your gods value people's lives,
Tanrılarınız insanların hayatlarına değer veriyorsa,
then wouldn't they have contempt for these ceremonies too?!
o zaman bu ayinlere de tiksinti duymalılar, değil mi?!
Give me some time!
Bana zaman verin!
I'll banish this so-called curse of yours!
Bu lanet dediğiniz şeyi kaldıracağım!
And if I can't, you can deal with us as you see fit!
Yapamazsam bize istediğinizi yapabilirsiniz!
What nonsense!
Saçmalık!
You think you're a god or something?!
Seni köpek, kendini tanrı falan mı sanıyorsun?!
In return, if I do save this village from tragedy,
Karşılığında, şayet bu köyü felaketten kurtarırsam...
swear to me you'll abolish this ritual!
bu ayinleri sonlandıracağınıza ant için!
Are you finished?
Bitirdin mi?
Such nonsense!
Koca bir zırva!
Your life ends here!
Hayatın burada sona erecek!
Let him try!
Bırak denesin!
H-Huh?
H-Ha?
What are you saying?!
Ne diyorsun?
He has until tomorrow evening. If he fails, their lives are forfeit.
Bu adamların kaderi yarın akşam belli olacak.
That's all I need!
İhtiyacım olan tek şey bu!
Come sunset tomorrow, it's "goodbye, world!"
Yarın gün batımında, "elveda dünya" diyeceğiz!
Have faith in the commodore!
Komodor'a güvenin!
Say, miss.
Hey, hanımefendi.
You must have it pretty rough too, being born in this village.
İşler senin için de zor olmalı. Burada doğmuş olman çok yazık.
Yeah!
Aynen!
With your looks, you could have married an aristocrat!
Sendeki bu güzellikle bir soyluyla evlenebilirdin!
Knock it off, guys! Can't you read the room?!
Yeter! Hiç nezaket duyunuz yok mu?
Who is he?
Kim o?
Oh, you mean the commodore?
Oh? Komodoru mu kastediyorsun?
That's Mont Blanc Noland.
Mont Blanc Noland.
A renowned explorer, and a botanist.
Epey ünlü bir kaşiftir. Ayrıca yetenekli bir bitki bilimcidir.
He visits uncharted islands to document and research new plants.
Yeni bitkileri belgelemek ve araştırmak için keşfedilmemiş adaları ziyaret eder.
He's pretty much a hero back home.
Memlekette kahraman sayılır.
But he's too kindhearted...
Ama çok iyi bir adamdır...
His biggest flaw is that he can't ignore stuff like this!
Bu gibi durumlara bir türlü sırt çeviremez!
We do trust him, though!
Yine de ona güveniyoruz!
Why didn't you let Kalgara kill him?!
Niye Kalgara'nın onu öldürmesine izin vermedin?
The answer will make itself known tomorrow.
Aradığınız cevabı yarın alacaksınız.
He says he'll save our village.
Köyü kurtaracağını söyledi.
There is no harm in waiting.
Beklemekle bir şey kaybetmeyiz.
How can you be so carefree?!
Nasıl bu kadar gamsız olabilirsin?
You'll listen to him, but not to the priest's last words?!
Başkeşişin sözlerini görmezden gelip o adama güvendin.
Kalgara! Say something!
Kalgara! Bir şey söyle!
If I sense the village is in even the slightest danger,
Köy için en ufak bir tehlike hissedersem,
I'll take that man's head before sunset tomorrow.
onu öldürmek için yarın akşamı beklemeyeceğim.
I do not have the power to hear the voices of the gods...
Tanrıların seslerini duyma gücüm yok.
However...
Ancak...
even I can hear the words of an earnest man.
akıllı bir adamın sözlerini duyabilirim.
That is all.
Hepsi bu.
Should you really be up?
Niye hâlâ uyanıksın?
I'm all better...
İyileştim.
Great Warrior Kalgara...
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara...
What does "progress" mean?
"Gelişim" nedir?
Here we are!
Buldum!
A cona tree!
Kona ağacı!
I'd be surprised if there wasn't one in such a big forest!
Elbette bu kadar büyük bir ormanda bulabilirim.
Earthquake!
Deprem!
It's really happening!
Geliyor! Gerçekten geliyor!
It's God Kashi's curse!
Bu Tanrı Kashi'nin öfkesi!
Let us out of here!
Çıkarın bizi buradan!
This is bad...
Durum berbat.
The forest floor has sunk...
Ormanın tabanı çöküyor.
It looks like the island is about to tear apart!
Görünüşe göre ada parçalanmak üzere!
Aren't you a fine sight?
Ne güzel görünüyorsun.
It seems the gods have delivered you a crushing blow themselves!
Anlaşılan o ki, tanrıların sillesini bizzat yemişsin!
In that case, these gods...
Öyleyse tanrıların...
aren't that great... after all...
söylediğin kadar güçlü değiller gibi.
They don't even have the strength... to kill a single person...
Tek bir adamı öldürecek güçleri bile yok.
You're stubborn.
İnatçısın.
Sorry, but could you get lost?
Üzgünüm ama çekip gider misin?
I don't feel like looking at you!
Şu an yüzünü görmek istemiyorum.
I... must hurry to the village!
Hemen... köye gitmeliyim.
Amusing.
İlginç.
I think I'll watch this play out.
Sanırım bu oyunu izleyeceğim.
Squirm out if you can!
Çıkabilirsen çık!
Another warrior has perished...
Bir savaşçı daha can verdi...
And right after that earthquake...
Hem de o depremin hemen ardından...
Damn it!
Kahretsin!
You're the evil spirits!
Sizler kötü ruhlarsınız!
We'll decide your fate right now!
Akıbetinize şimdi karar vereceğiz!
Th-This wasn't the agreement! Stop!
B-Böyle anlaşmamıştık! Durun!
Stop!
Yapmayın!
Look out!
Dikkat edin!
Seto! Move aside!
Seto! Çekil yolumuzdan!
What are you doing?!
Ne yapıyorsun!?
The Shandian warriors I look up to...
Değer verdiğim Shandia savaşçıları...
have much more pride than this!
bundan daha fazla onurlu olmalı!
Kid...
Çocuk...
When this sun lowers in the west and sinks once again...
Güneş batıya devrilip yeniden söndüğünde,
your men's lives will be offered to the gods!
adamlarının canı tanrılara armağan edilecek!
Damn it!
Kahretsin!
The earth certainly swallowed you up quite nicely!
Toprak kaymasına yakalanman nasıl da yerinde bir durum.
Truly an act of the gods!
Bu gerçekten tanrıların işi.
That you're still alive is beyond belief!
Hâlâ yaşıyor olman şaşırtıcı.
He shifted the earth?!
Yeri mi hareket ettirdi?
Prepare for the ceremony!
Ayin için hazırlanın!
Take every last sacrifice to the altar!
Kurbanları sunağa götürün!
Hey, wait a little longer!
Hey, az daha bekleyin!
The commodore will be back! Just two more hours! No, one hour! Please!
Komodor geri dönecek! Sadece iki saat verin! Hayır, bir! Lütfen!
Why do we have to be burned at the stake?!
Bize neden kazıkta yakılmak reva görülüyor?!
The sun is setting.
Güneş batıyor.
The ceremony should be starting soon.
Birazdan ayine başlayacaklar.
How pathetic!
Acınası bir durumdasın.
Is this wretch the same man who defied the gods?
Tanrılara meydan okuyan adam bu mu?
What are you so afraid of?
Neden korkuyorsun?
What?!
Ne?!
You tremble before intangible fears,
Soyut korkular karşısında titreyip,
throwing away people's lives for a false sense of comfort!
sahte bir teselli için insanları kurban ediyorsunuz!
False sense of comfort?!
Sahte teselli mi?!
Your sacrifices are nothing but pointless deaths!
Kurbanlarınızın hepsi manasız birer ölüm!
We have lived this way for centuries now!
Biz asırlardır bu sayede hayatta kaldık!
That doesn't mean it's right!
Söylediğin bunu haklı çıkarmaz!
Silence, outsider!
Kapa' çeneni, yabancı!
However great your gods may be,
Tanrılarınız ne kadar büyük olursa olsun,
people's lives are even more sacred!
insanların hayatı daha değerlidir!
Take the sacrifices to the altar!
Kurbanları sunağa götürün!
Burn them at the stake and send them into the heavens!
Onları kazıkta yakın ve cennete gönderin!
Commodore!
Komodor!
We're gonna be burned alive!
Diri diri yanacağız!
You can send an innocent girl to her death...
O masum kızı vicdanınız rahat bir şekilde...
without any second thoughts, so I doubt you'd understand!
ölüme gönderebiliyorsunuz; o yüzden sizi anlayacağımı hiç sanmıyorum!
What you're doing is inhuman!
Yaptığınız şey barbarca!
No second thoughts, you say?
Öyle mi diyorsun?
The girl from yesterday...
Dünkü kurtardığın kız...
was my daughter!
öz kızım olsa bile mi?!
You would tell your own daughter to end her life?!
Kendi kızına hayatını feda etmesini mi emrettin?!
You're the ones who can't understand the immense power
Sen ve tayfan, tanrıların sözlerini duyan başkeşişin gücünü...
of our priest's divine words!
asla anlayamazsınız!
It is our village's sacred duty to obey them!
Onlara itaat etmek köyümüzün kutsal görevidir!
I can't plead for her life just because she's my daughter!
Sırf benim kızım diye onun hayatı için yalvaramam!
It's smaller... It must be the child of God Kashi!
Öncekinden daha küçük. Tanrı Kashi'nin oğlu mu?
The gods' own blood has come to pass judgment on you!
Tanrının kanını döktüğün için hakkındaki hükmü vermeye geldi!
Judgment, my ass!
Kıçımın hükmü!
Sixty years ago, we lost hundreds of thousands of lives in our homeland
60 sene önce ülkemde, köyünü kasıp kavuran aynı salgın...
to the same tree fever that is ravaging your village now!
ağaç ateşi, 100 bin insanın hayatını aldı!
However! In recent years, we've had absolutely no deaths to this disease!
Ama şimdi, tek bir insan bile bu hastalıktan dolayı ölmeyecek!
Do you know why?!
Niye biliyor musun?!
Because we discovered a cure for it!
Çünkü bir tedavi bulduk!
What I'm holding in my right hand is the bark of a cona tree!
Sağ elimde, kona ağacının kabuğunu tutuyorum!
The conine I can extract from it is the cure!
Bu kabuktan koniin, yani ilaç elde edebiliriz!
If I return with this, I can save the village!
Bunu götürürsek köyün kurtulacak!
Do you know how much time has been spent by people all around the world,
Dünyanın dört bir yanındaki insanların buna ne kadar ömür harcadığını...
and how many victims there have been?!
ve kaç kurban verildiğini biliyor musun?!
Your people are disregarding the incredible progress we've made!
Siz bu harika gelişimi hiçe sayıyorsunuz!
That's why I'm saying your "ceremonies" are an affront to humanity's progress!
İşte bu yüzden, ayinleriniz insanlığın gelişimine bir hakarettir!
Will I die by judgment, or by accident?!
Hükmen mi öleceğim, yoksa kazara mı?!
Will your village die by curse, or by disease?!
Köyünüz lanetten mi yoksa hastalıktan mı ölecek?!
Are you that afraid of your gods?!
Tanrılardan o kadar mı korkuyorsunuz?!
Even I can hear the words of an earnest man.
Akıllı bir adamın sözlerini duyabilirim.
Tell me...
Cevap ver...
what did I just kill?!
Öldürdüğüm şey nedir?
A snake.
Yılan.
No!
Yanlış!
I broke our commandments and felled a god!
Kutsal kuralı bozup bir tanrı öldürdüm!
But you call it a snake, and our deadly curse a curable disease!
Ama ona yılan, ölümcül lanetimize de tedavi edilebilir bir hastalık diyorsun!
Will you really save my beloved village?!
Gerçekten değerli köyümü kurtaracak mısın?!
Can you save it?!
Kurtarabilir misin?!
I can!
Evet!
Jaya, the Grand Line 400 Years Ago
Jaya, Grand Line 400 Yıl Önce
Kalgara The Great Warrior of Shandora
Kalgara Shandora'nın Şanlı Savaşçısı
Elsewhere on the Grand Line...
Grand Line'da bir yer...
Commodore Mont Blanc Noland Exploration Ship Kingdom of Lvneel, North Blue
Mont Blanc Noland Keşif Gemisi Komodoru Lvneel Krallığı, Kuzey Mavi
Commodore Mont Blanc Noland Exploration Ship Kingdom of Lvneel, North Blue
Mont Blanc Noland Keşif Gemisi Komodoru Lvneel Krallığı, Kuzey Mavi
Commodore Mont Blanc Noland Exploration Ship Kingdom of Lvneel, North Blue
Mont Blanc Noland Keşif Gemisi Komodoru Lvneel Krallığı, Kuzey Mavi
Jaya, the Grand Line May 21, 1122 of the Pelagic Calendar
Jaya, Grand Line 21 Mayıs 1222 Deniz Çağı
Jaya, the Grand Line May 21, 1122 of the Pelagic Calendar
Jaya, Grand Line 21 Mayıs 1222 Deniz Çağı
Jaya, the Grand Line May 21, 1122 of the Pelagic Calendar
Jaya, Grand Line 21 Mayıs 1222 Deniz Çağı
Dawn
Şafak